Guide to the H. Elliott McClure Papers, 1947-1989.
McClure, H. Elliott papers
- Series II: Banding Lists, Counts and Observation Files
  - Federal Hill, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Federal Hill, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Pangkor, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Gajah Puteh, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Kledang Saiong Forest, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Kuala Kangsar, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - King Gorge V National Park, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Japan Bird Tallies, 1950-1957 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Japan: Setagaya I, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Japan: Setagaya II, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Japan Lists, 1940-1966 (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Summary of bird tallies in Japan by Species, 1951-1953 (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Banding Lists and Blood Smears, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Sunday Market (Bangkok) Banded Birds, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Sunday Market (Bangkok) Banded Birds, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sunday Market (Bangkok) Bird Study, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sunday Market (Bangkok) Bird Study, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Price Lists and Information: Sunday Market Birds (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - YV Bulbul versus S Blue Robin (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Repeats, 1964-1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Papers Giving Weight and Moult Data; Recovery Data (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - British Bird Nesting Records, 1937-1959 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Birds Nests, Malaya, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Band Records, 1952-1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Ulu Gombak, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Ulu Gombak, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Field Trips: Singapore - Port Dickson, 1953, 1958, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lists to Tally (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Rantau Panjang, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Federal Hill, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Federal Hill, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mt. Brunchang Bird Records, 1957-1963 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Rantau Panchang, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Subang, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - En-route Rantau Panjang, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Rantau Panjang (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Federal Hill Summaries (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Summary of Nesting at Rantau Panjang (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Banding, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Ulu Gombak Tree Platform, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Ampang Road, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Ulu Gombak Tree Platform, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Ampang Road, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - En-route Rantau Panjang, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - En-route Rantau Panjang, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - En-route Rantau Panjang, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Rantau Panjang, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Enroute Rantau Panjang, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Notebook with hand-written summary table of every species McClure himself banded over 50 years, 1938-1993 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Table 1 for Report on Sunday Market, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photographs and Maps: Rantau Panjang (Box 28, Folder 62)
- Series III: Bird Banding - Khao Yai Bird Studies (Thailand)
  - 91-04-10 Zosteropidae Zosteropo palpebrosa (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 90-10-07 Dicacidae Ditaem chrysorrheum (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 90-01-08 Dicacidae Diceum concolor (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 90-01-12 Dicacidae Dicaeum ignipectus (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 90-01-02 Dicacidae Dicaeum agile (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 89-04-01 Nectariniidae Hippogramma hippogramica (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 89-05-03 Nectariniidae Nectarinia jugularis (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 89-05-01 Nectariniidae Nectarinia asiatica (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 89-03-07 Nectariniidae Arachnothera longirostra (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 89-01-13 Nectariniidae Aethopyga siparaja (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 89-02-04 Nectariniidae Anthreptes singalensis (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 89-01-11 Nectariniidae Aethopyga saturata (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 82-04-04 Motocilliidae Motacilla flava (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 82-03-01 Motacilliidae Dendronanthus indicus (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 82-04-01 Motacilliidae Motacilla alba (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 82-04-02 Motacilliidae Motacilla caspica (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 52-01-05 Motacilliidae Anthus novaeseelandiae (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 82-01-03 Motacilliidae Anthus hodgsoni (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 79-10-37 Muscicapidae Muscicapa sibirica (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 79-10-51 Muscicapidae Muscicapa westermani (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 79-10-18 Muscicapidae Muscicapa latirostris (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 79-10-53 Muscicapidae Muscicapa zanthopygia (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 79-10-27 Muscicapidae Muscicapa parva (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 79-17-04 Muscicapidae Jerpsiphona paradisi (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 79-10-44 Muscicapidae Muscicapa thalassina (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 79-06-01 Muscicapidae Hypothymis azurea (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 79-13-09 Muscicapidae Rhipidura perlata (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 79-03-01 Muscicapidae Culicicapa ceylonensis (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 79-10-02 Muscicapidae Muscicapa banyumas (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 84-01-01 Artamidae Artamus fusca (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 86-05-02 Sturmidae Gracula religiosa (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 86-02-01 Sturmidae Ampeliceps coronatus (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 86-10-09 Sturnidae Sturnus malabaricus (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 86-10-07 Sturmidae Sturnus javanidus (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 86-10-17 Sturmidae Sturnus sinensis (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 85-01-07 Laniidae Lanius nasutus (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 85-01-04 Laniidae Lanius cristatus (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 92-04-02 Columbidae Decula badia (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 42-12-08 Columbidae Treron phoenicoptera (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 42-11-06 Columbidae Streptophelia Tranquebarica (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 42-12-06 Columbidae Treron pompadora (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 42-12-04 Columbidae Treron curvirostra (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - 42-11-02 Columbidae Streptopelia chinensia (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - 42-07-04 Columbidae Macropygia unchall (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - 42-02-01 Columbidae Chalcophaps indica (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 59-14-13 Picidae Picus vittatus (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 59-14-05 Picidae Picus flarinueha (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 59-14-04 Picidae Picus erythropygius (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 59-14-03 Picidae Picus chloropus (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 59-14-02 Picidae Picus picuscanus (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 59-11-02 Picidae Mulleripicus pulverulentus (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 59-09-01 Picidae Meiglyptes jugularis (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 59-10-01 Picidae Micropternus brachyurus (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 59-05-01 Picidae Dryocopus javenensis (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 56-04-02 Picidae Dinopium javanense (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 59-02-02 Picidae Chrysocolaptes lucidus (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 63-01-03 Hirundinidae Delichon urbica (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 63-02-06 Hirundinidae Hirundo rustica (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 63-02-02 Hirundinidae Hirundo daurica (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 60-06-01 Eurylaimidae Serilophus lunatus (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 60-05-01 Eurylaimidae Psarisomus dalhousiae (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 60-04-01 Eurylaimidae Eurylaimus javanicus (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 78-12-08 Sylviidae Orthotomus sutorius (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 78-12-03 Sylviidae Orthotomus cucllatus (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 78-12-01 Sylviidae Orthotomus atrogularis (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 78-04-11 Sylviidae Cettia squameiceps (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 78-14-13 Sylviidae Prinia sudflara (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 78-13-25 Sylviidae Phylloscopus schwarpi (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 78-13-24 Sylviidae Phylloscopus ricketti (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 78-13-23 Sylviidae Phylloscopus reguloides (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 78-13-14 Sylviidae Phylloscopus inornatus (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 78-13-11 Sylviidae Phylloscopus fuscatus (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 78-13-30 Sylviidae Phylloscopus coronatus (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 78-13-30 Sylviidae Phylloscopus trochiloides (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 78-13-26 Sylviidae Phylloscopus subaffinis (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 78-13-01 Sylviidae Phylloscopus aedon (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 78-13-00 Sylviidae Phylloscopus sp (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 78-14-07 Sylviidae Prinia flaviventris (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 78-14-09 Sylviidae Prniia hodgsoni (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 78-14-11 Sylviidae Prinia rufeseens (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 78-16-03 Sylviidae Seieereus kurkii (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 78-05-01 Sylviidae Cisticola exilis (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 74-03-02 Aegithinidae Irena puella (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 74-02-01 Aegithinidae Chloropsis aurifrons (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 74-02-02 Aegithinidae Chloropaia eochinchinensis (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 74-01-01 Aegithinidae Aegithinia lafresneyei (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 73-02-05 Pycnonotidae Hypsipetes flavala (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 73-02-07 Pycnonotidae Hypsipetes madagasceariensis (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 73-02-12 Pycnonotidae Hypsipetes propinguus (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 73-01-05 Pycnonotidae Criniger pallidus (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 73-03-01 Pycnonotidae Pycnonotus atriceps (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 73-03-02 Pycnonotidae Pycnonotus aurigaster (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 73-03-16 Pycnonotidae Pycnonotus melanicterus (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 73-03-10 Pycnonotidae Pycnonotus finlaysoni (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 73-03-13 Pycnonotidae Pycnonotus jocosus (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 31-14-07 Scolopacidae Scolopax rusticola (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - 13-13-01 Scolopacidae Scolopax rusticola (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - 31-04- -- Scolopacidae Capella (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - 31-01-01 Scolopacidae Aotitis hypoleucus (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - 24-05-01 Rallidae Gallinula chloropus (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - 24-01-05 Rallidae Amaurornis phoeniearus (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - 64-02-02 Campephagidae Coracina fimbriata (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 64-02-10 Campephagidae Coracina polioptera (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 64-02-06 Campephagidae Coracina melaschista (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 64-06-01 Campephagidae Tephrodornis pondicerianus (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 64-03-02 Campephagidae Hemipus picatus (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 64-05-06 Campephagidae Pericrocotus flammus (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 64-05-03 Capephagidae Pericrocotus divaricatus (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 43-03-04 Psittacidae Loriculus vernalis (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 44-03-08 Cuculidae Centropus toulou (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 44-10-08 Cuculidae Phaenicophapus Pristis (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 44-03-06 Cuculidae Centropus sinensis (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 44-06-01 Cuculidae Clamator coromanda (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 44-12-01 Cuculidae Surniculus lugubris (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 44-01-01 Cuculidae Cacomantis marulinus (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 44- -- - -- Cuculidae Carpococcyx renauldi (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 48-02-01 Caprimulgidae Eurostopodus macrotis (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - 48-01-08 Caprimulgidae Caprimulgus macrurus (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - 48-01-04 Caprimulgidae Caprimulgus indicus (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 46-02-03 Strigidae Athena brama (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - 46-04-01 Strigidae Glaucidium brodiei (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - 46-04-02 Strigidae Glaucidium euuloideo (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - 46-05-03 Strigidae Ketupa zeylonensis (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - 46-07-03 Strigidae Ninox sculalata (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - 46-09-01 Strigidae Olus bakkamoena (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - 46-09-08 Strigidae Olus spilocephalus (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - 68-04-01 Paridae Melanochlora sultanea (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 70-02-05 Sittidae Sitta frontalis (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 54-01-01 Coraciidae Coracias benghalensis (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - 54-02-01 Coraciidae Eurystomus orientalis (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - 53-01-02 Meropidae Merops leschenaulti (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - 53-01-04 Meropidae Merops philippinus (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - 53-02-02 Meropidae Nydiornis athertoni (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - 51-01-05 Trogonidae Harpactes erythrocephalus (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - 51-0107 Trogonidae Harpactes oreskios (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - 93-01-03 Ploceidae Erythrura prasina (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - 93-02-09 Ploceidae Lonchura striata (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - 67-01-03 Corvidae Cissa chinensis (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - 67-02-05 Corvidae Corvus macrorhynchus (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - 67-06-01 Corvidae Garrulus glandarius (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - 52-01-01 Alcedinidae Alcedo atthis (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - 52-01-05 Alcedinidae Alcedo meninting (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - 52-04-06 Alcedinidae Haleyon pileata (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - 52-04-08 Alcedinidae Haleyon smyrensis (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - 52-05-01 Alcedinidae Lacedo pulchella (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - 52-06-02 Alcedinidae Pelargopsis capensis (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - 92-07-01 Fringillidae Emberiza aureola (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - 56-03-01 Bucerotidae Anthracoceros albirostris (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 56-05-01 Bucerotidae Buceros bicornis (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 56-09-03 Bucerotidae Rhyticeros undulatus (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 57-02-19 Capitonidae Megalaima raffesi (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - 57-02-11 Capitonidae Megalaima incognita (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 57-02-07 Capitonidae Megalaima faiostricta (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 57-02-02 Capitonidae Megalaima asiatica (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 57-02-02 Capitonidae Megalaima asiatica (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - 57-02- -- Capitonidae Megalaima sp. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 77-06-05 Turdidae Enicurus schistaceus (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - 77-06-02 Turdidae Enicorus leschenaulti (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - 77-07-03 Turdidae Erithacus calliope (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - 77-10-02 Turdidae Monticola gularis (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - 77-16-07 Turdidae saxicola Torquata) (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - 77-07-05 Turdidae Erithacus cyane (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - 77-12-02 Turdidae Myophonus caeruleus (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - 77-05-03 Turdidae Copsychus malabaricus (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - 77-10-05 Turdidae Monticola solitarius (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - 49-01-02 Apodidae Apus affinis (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 49-01-05 Apodidae Apus pacificus (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 49-02-01 Apodidae Chaetura cochinchinensis (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 49-02-02 Apodidae Chaetura gigantea (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 49-03-01 Apodidae Chaetura brevirostris (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 49-04-01 Apodidae Cypsiurus parrus (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 71-15-02 Timaliidae Macronous gularis (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 71-10-20 Timaliidae Garrulax leucolophus (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 71-10-08 Timaliidae Garrulax chinensis (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 71-10-29 Timaliidae Garrulax monilegerus (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 71-10-35 Timaliidae Garrulax peetoralis (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 71-23-06 Timaliidae Pomatorhinus schisticeps (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 71-21-05 Timaliidae Pellprneum ruficeps (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 71-32-01 Timaliidae Trichastoma abbotti (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 71-35-09 Timaliidae Yuhina zantholeuca (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - 65-01-07Dicruridae Dicrurus leucophaeus (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - 65-01-02 Dicruridae Dicrurus aeneus (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - 65-01-01 Dicruridae Dicrurus adsimilis (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - 65-01-10 Dicruridae Dicrurus remifer (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - 65-01-08 Dicruridae Dicrurus hottentotus (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - 65-01-09 Dicruridae Dicrurus paradiseus (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - 66-01-02 Oriolidae Oriolus chinensis (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Tallies, Data and Analysis, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Birds of Khao Yai: Manuscript and Banding Lists (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Banding Lists, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Khao Yai Pictures (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Summary of Khao Yai Studies, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Biomass and Predation at Khao Yai (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Khao Yai Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Plants of Khao Yai National Park (Box 28, Folder 61)
- Series IV: Avian Disease: Parasites and Ectoparasites
  - Blood Parasites of Birds in Malaya, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Avian Malaria in Japan, July - December 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mosquito Entymology Training Course, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Comparative Study of Avian Haematozoa by Area, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Bird Malaria (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Ectoparasites of Birds and Rodents (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Avian Serological Data from Japan, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Series V: Recovery Files
  - Recoveries by Country of Origin and Country of Recovery (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Philippines, May 1968 - July 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Philippines, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Philippines, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Philippines, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Philippines, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence Files, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (Philippines), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Philippines, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Philippines, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Philippines, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Burma, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Laos and Burma, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cambodia, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Laos, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Laos, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Hong Kong, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Hong Kong, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hong Kong, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Indonesia, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Indonesia, 21 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hong Kong, Singapore, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Russia, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - USSR, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Indonesia, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Indonesia, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Unreported Ring Recoveries, 1944-45, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - DPR Korea; Pending Recoveries - Foreign, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Burma, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Indonesia, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Malaysia, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Recoveries, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Malaya, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - East Pakistan, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - East Pakistan, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - East Pakistan, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Australia, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Indonesia, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Vietnam, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - USSR, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - USSR, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - USSR, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Russia, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Japan, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Japan, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Japan, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Sarawak, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Sabah, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Malaysia, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Thailand, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Thailand, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Thailand, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Thailand, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - USA, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - USA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Alaska and America, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Alaska and America, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - America, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - USSR, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - USSR, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - USSR, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Russia, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Tonga Island, South West pacific, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - New Guinea, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Answered Recovery Letters, June 1975 - January 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Pending Recoveries - Sarawak, Sabah, 1969-1971, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Taiwan, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Taiwan, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Korea, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Korea, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Australia, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Australia, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Australia, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Australia, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - India, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Hong Kong, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Hong Kong, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Hong Kong, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Yoichi Kenzaki, Japan, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Japan, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Japan, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Japan, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Korea, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Korea, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Japan, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Korea, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Korea, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Korea, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - North Korea, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Laos, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Malaysia, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Penang, Malaysia, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Perak, Malaysia, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Malaysia, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Malaysia, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Parit, Malaysia, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - New Guinea, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Thailand, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Thailand, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Singapore, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Thailand, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Singapore, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Singapore, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Singapore, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Singapore, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Singapore, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Taiwan, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Sabah, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Okinawa, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Singapore, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Philippines, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Philippines, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Philippines, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Philippines, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Philippines, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Philippines, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 55)
- Series VI: Arthropods
  - Batu Caves
    - Plates and Charts (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Plates: Small Orders (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Plates: Hemiptera (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Plates: Diptera (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Plates: Hymenoptera (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Plates: Coleoptera (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Plates: Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Field Notes (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Illustrations (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Species Identification (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Taxonomists Identifications (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Taxonomists Identifications and Summaries (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Homoptera (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Identifications, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mosquitoes of Rantau Panjang (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hemiptera (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Lepidoptera (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Diptera (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Coleoptera (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Hymenoptera (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Neuroptera (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Orthoptera (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Lepsidoptera (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Hippoboscid Flies at Camarillo and Camarillo Grove, 1977-1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Mosquito Collection, Sugiyama, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mosquito Study, Yaacob, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Mosquito Studies, Usamru, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Mosquito Studies, Manikumar, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Old Reports and Field Studies of Insects (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Handwritten Field Notes on Insect Collection in the US: Hibernation Collection Record, 1931-1933 (Box 28)
- Series VII: Diaries and Correspondence
  - Shipment/Mail Records
    - Silliman University, Philippines, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - Tunchai University, Taiwan, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - USAMRU Institute for Medical Research, Malaysia, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - Yamashina Institute and Museum, Japan, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - Kyung Hee University, Korea, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - National Museum, Philippines, 1964-1970 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, September 1964 - February 1972 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Diaries and Notes
    - Field notes, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Photocopy of Personal, Hand-written Diary (Covers Asia and US Retirement, Latest Entry: 1996) (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Photocopy of Personal, Hand-written Diary (Contd.) (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Photocopy of Personal, Hand-written Diary (Contd.) (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Myakojima Journal and Photographs, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Fifty Years of Bird Banding: Copy of McClure's handwritten summary table of birds he banded over 50 years, 1938-1989 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Handwritten Diary of Banded Birds, sorted by name, 1951-1955 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence Files
    - Philippines, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Don Bleitz, December 1967 - March 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Letha Grenundike, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - P. Murrell, National Parks and Wildlife Service, Tasmania, July 1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - L. Anne Cooley, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mark Crawford, 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kathleen Clement, 1989, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)